[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This man is probably most famous for his work on The Godfather series. He was nominated for best cinematographer for The Godfather Part III (1990).", "correct_answer": "Gordon Willis", "incorrect_answers": ["Roger Pratt", "William H. Daniels", "Roger Deakins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Kasson Metric Act of 1866 made the Metric System the official system of the USA, although it was repealed in 1873.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of Dashs teacher in The Incredibles?", "correct_answer": "Bernie", "incorrect_answers": ["Barney", "Buzz", "Bert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to urban legends, at Santa Fes Loretto Chapel, this structure defies the laws of physics, standing without any support.", "correct_answer": "A spiral staircase", "incorrect_answers": ["A 12 foot tall mirror", "A stained glass window depicting Jesus", "A stained glass window depicting St. Joseph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Some of the fake names used by the narrator in the film Fight Club are names of the characters in Planet of the Apes, as well as characters played by which actor?", "correct_answer": "Robert De Niro", "incorrect_answers": ["Al Pacino", "Cary Grant", "Tom Cruise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Kingpin, Roy Munson acquired what nickname because of his rubber hand?", "correct_answer": "Rubber Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Rubber Hand", "Captain Hook", "One Hand Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The album Whitesnake 1987 by Whitesnake included three of these songs. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Fool For Your Loving", "incorrect_answers": ["Here I Go Again", "Still Of The Night", "Is This Love"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mount Vesuvius, that is notorious for the destruction of two Roman cities in the year 79, was linked most closely to which hero and demigod?", "correct_answer": "Hercules", "incorrect_answers": ["Asclepius", "Apollo", "Zeus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturns atmosphere consists mostly of these two gases.", "correct_answer": "hydrogen and helium", "incorrect_answers": ["hydrogen and methane", "methane and ammonia", "helium and nitrogen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Earth years add up to a galactic year?", "correct_answer": "250 Million", "incorrect_answers": ["180 Million", "350 Million", "400 Million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Watchmen universe what war is Dr. Manhattan credited with winning?", "correct_answer": "Vietnam War", "incorrect_answers": ["The Battle of Bunker Hill", "World War II", "The Showdown of Antgio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular tourist destination stands at the foot of the Maritime Alps?", "correct_answer": "Monte Carlo", "incorrect_answers": ["Verona", "Vatican City", "Lisbon"]}]